https://www.pregcare.com/privacy-policy

Text 1-403-269-3110
The following online privacy policy is to protect and secure the personal information you provide to our organization online.
Awareness
The Calgary Pregnancy Care Cenre provides this online policy to make sure you are aware of our security practices and to inform you of the way your information is collected and used. We also provide you with the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list, if you desire to do so.
Information we collect
There are two different ways in which we collect information from visitors on our website:
From persons interested in requesting information or materials from our organization
From our online donations
The online information that we collect includes name, address, city, province, postal code, telephone number, e-mail address, and, in the case of online giving, the credit card number and expiration date. In order to continuously improve your service and tailor our subsequent communications to you, we may also ask you to provide us with enough information regarding your demographics, comments, professional interests, and contact preferences.
How is the information used
The Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre uses your information to understand your needs with the aim of providing you better service. We may use your information to complete a transaction or issue you an income tax receipt for a donation. If you so desire, we may also use this information to update you on projects and activities of the organization. Credit card numbers are used only for donation or payment processing and are not retained for any other purposes. We also provide you the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list, if you desire to do so. Please review the corresponding section of this privacy policy below.
No sharing of personal information
The Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre never sells, rents, leases, or exchanges your personal information with other organizations. The Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre assures you that the identity of all who contact us through this Web site will be kept confidential. Use of personal information will be limited to the internal purposes of the Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre and only to further the activities and purposes of the Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre.
Security
The Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the proper use of information, we have established and implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. The Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre uses Internet Encryption Software, Thawte protocol is used when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. Any information you enter is encrypted at your browser, sent over the public Internet in encrypted form, then de-encrypted at our server. Once we receive your credit card information, it is accessible only to a small number of trusted Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre staff who have been specially trained in processing this information.
Tweet
Calgary Care Centre
205, 925 - 7th Ave, SWCalgary, AB, T2P 1A5
Phone: 403-269-3112
Email: info@pregcare.com
Office Hours
Mon 9:00am - 5:00pm
Tues 9:00am - 8:00pm
Monday - Thursday 10:00 am - 4:00 pm (Closed Friday)
and participants. Donate Now!
Sign up for our Newsletter
Call or Text:
© 2018 Calgary Pregnancy Care Centre · Privacy Policy · Disclaimer ·
